bonzobox.com 2014-06-19

# BonzoBox – It's Your Homepage

Thank you for visiting www.bonzobox.com (" _Site_ "). This Site is a service made available to you by Bonzobox, LLC, a California limited liability company (" _we_ " or " _us_ "). We are committed to protecting and safeguarding your privacy. The purpose of this privacy statement (" _Privacy Statement_ ") is to inform you about the types of information we might collect from you when you visit our Site, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct, that information.

By using our Site, you acknowledge acceptance of the Privacy Statement in effect at the time of your use.

##### What Information We Collect and How We Use It

There are two kinds of information we collect on our Site: (i) Personally Identifiable Information and (ii) Aggregate Information. " _Personally Identifiable Information_ " refers to information that lets us know specifically who you are. In general, you can visit our Site without telling us who you are or revealing any Personally Identifiable Information. You may, however, voluntarily provide Personally Identifiable Information (such as name, e-mail address, and country of origin) for us to contact you, including via e-mail, to respond to your comments or inquiries. In such event, we might maintain a record of your contact, including such Personally Identifiable Information, in a file specific to you. We use this information to provide better service in the event you contact us again.

" _Aggregate Information_ " refers to information that does not by itself identify you as a specific individual. Such information would include the Uniform Resource Identifier ("URI") of the Web site that referred you to our Site, your Internet Protocol ("IP") address (a number automatically assigned to your computer whenever you surf the Web), your operating system and browser type, and any search terms that you enter on our Site. Our server aggregates this information in order to monitor the level of activity on our Site, evaluate its effectiveness, and improve the content of our Site in order to make your visit an easy and enjoyable experience.

We may collect, compile, store, publish, promote, report, or otherwise disclose or use any Aggregate Information, provided that, such information does not personally identify you. We do not correlate any Personally Identifiable Information with the Aggregate Information that we collect on our Site. If we do correlate any Aggregate Information to you, it will be protected like any other Personally Identifiable Information under this Privacy Statement.

##### Sharing Your Information

Except as set forth in this Privacy Statement, we do not sell or otherwise retransmit any Personally Identifiable Information we collect from your on our Site unless we have your permission. Any Personally Identifiable Information you provide to us will be stored in our databases in the United States.

From time to time, we may be required to provide Personally Identifiable Information in response to court order, subpoena, or government investigation. We also reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful. We may release Personally Identifiable Information when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary to enforce or apply our Terms of Use or to protect the rights, property, and safety of others and ourselves.

##### Using Your Information

We may use your Personally Identifiable information to contact you directly via e-mail, facsimile, telephone or mail. If you do not wish us to contact you, please contact us as described below and tell us that you do not wish us to contact you.

##### Accessing and Correcting Your Information

We take reasonable measures to ensure that any Personally Identifiable Information we collect on our Site is accurate, current, complete, and reliable for its intended use. If you wish to update or otherwise correct Personally Identifiable Information you have provided to us, you may contact us as described below.

##### Protecting Your Information

We are committed to take reasonable steps to protect Personally Identifiable Information you provide to us through this Site from loss, misuse and unauthorized access. We employ physical, electronic, and managerial processes to safeguard and secure your information.

##### Use of Cookies On This Site

A "cookie" is a small data file transferred to your computer's hard drive that allows a Web site to respond to you as an individual, gathering and remembering information about your preferences in order to tailor its operation to your needs, likes and dislikes. Overall, cookies are safe, as they only identify your computer to customize your Web experience. Accepting a cookie does not provide access to your computer or any Personally Identifiable Information about you, other than the information you chose to share. Other servers cannot read them, nor can they be used to deliver a virus.

Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually adjust yours to notify you of cookie placement requests, refuse certain cookies, or decline cookies completely.

Our Site does send cookies to your computer's hard drive to enhance your experience when visiting our Site.

##### Use of ActiveX and Java Applets and other Similar Programs On This Site

ActiveX programs and Java applets, including Adobe Flash, are executable programs transferred to your computer's hard drive that cause your computer to perform functions in connection with your visit to a Web site.

Our Site may transfer ActiveX programs, Java applets or other similar programs to your computer’s hard drive to enhance your experience when visiting our Site.

##### Links To Other Web Sites

Our Site may contain hyperlinks to other Web sites. These hyperlinks are provided solely as a convenience to you. We have not reviewed and do not endorse or accept any responsibility for the content, or accessibility of resources available on, any other Web site. This Privacy Statement does not cover the information practices of those Web sites linked to our Site, nor do we control their content or privacy policies. We suggest that you carefully review the privacy policies of each site you visit.

##### Changes To This Privacy Statement

We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions of this Privacy Statement, at any time. Updated versions of our Privacy Statement will be posted here on our Site and are effective immediately. The date of the newest version is posted below. It is your responsibility to check this Privacy Statement periodically for changes, especially before you submit any Personally Identifiable Information to us.

Copyright 2008 by Bonzobox, LLC

Date of Last Update to Privacy Statement: February 29, 2008.

##### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, please email us at info@bonzobox.com. We will make every reasonable effort to address your concerns and remedy any problems you bring to our attention.
